

CONTACT

+237680802387



njigoudonald00@gmail.com



Logpom-Bangos

EDUCATION

2020-2023

HIBMAT UNIVERSITY INSTITUTE OF BUEA (HUIB)

• BACHELOR'S OF TECHNOLOGY

2012 - 2019

COLLEGE MODERNE BILINGUE DE LAUREAT

HIGH SCHOOL

EXPERTISE

- Search Engine Optimization
- Critical thinking
- Digital marketing
- · Wordpress website building

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Sports
- Travelling

SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Attention to details
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Critical Thinking

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- French (Fluent)

NJIGOU DONALD LOBE

SEO SPECIALIST

PROFILE

With nearly 5 years of experience doing SEO, I have learned and acquired an extensive understanding of different aspects of SEO, from understanding Google algorithm changes to building solid SEO strategies. During this period I honed different skills such as content optimization, link acquisition, competitor analysis as well as some other skills such as critical thinking and learning to work as a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance

2023 - PRESENT

SEO Expert

- · Worked with various companies, on different aspects of their businesses and then built websites about the various businesses so as to increase sales and visibility.
- SEO(search engine optimizer): Optimized different registered websites in different search engines in order to increase visibility, sales and also rank keywords of websites in first pages of different search engines.

SELF EMPLOYED

2021 - 2023

SEO Executive

- · Worked with different freelancers on a large E-commerce website, who sold clothes and shoes online.
- · Execute and oversee SEO strategies.
- Performed keyword research, optimized on-page elements, and built high-quality backlinks to increase organic traffic.

Freelance

2020 - 2021

social media manager

- · work closely with companies to help boost their online presence using social media and SEO verticals.
- Increased sales on websites using various linked social mediae which brought up expected audiences.